Daniil Shvedov

Toronto | 1 (437) 6632700 | miliereya32@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/web-daniil-shvedov

Position of Interest - Web Developer

About:

Full-stack Developer with over 5 years experience in crafting, testing and maintaining web applications. Gained experience in different commercial arias of web development and equipped with the most relevant tech stack. Able to work both independently and as part of a team.

Hard Skills:

TypeScript

JavaScript

Python

Next.js

React

Redux

Three.js

WebSocket

Nest.js

Express.js

RabbitMQ

SQL / NoSQL Databases

Docker

Unit / E2E tests

Figma

Work Experience:

Senior Full-stack Developer, "Startupium"

(06/2023 - 02/2024)

Russia, Moscow

- Planned and implemented dashboards/admin panels/work flows.
- Established rules for code purity and quality.
- Optimized for search engines and improved website performance.
- Reviewed over 100 commits/merge requests.
- Transferred and upgraded features from the old version of the site.

Tech summary: TypeScript, PHP, Laravel, Next.js, Redux, Feature Sliced Design, Code review.

Middle Full-stack Developer, "CITY-TRADE LTD"

(02/2021 - 05/2023)

Ukraine, Dnipro

- Built over 5 parsers / readers for different types of documents and templates.
- Accelerated the company's internal processes by 60%.
- Designed and coded 3 websites from zero for company industries.
- Worked directly with clients and other clients.

Tech summary: TypeScript, JavaScript, React, Redux, Express.js, Nest.js, MongoDB, MySQL.

Developer, "Freelance"

(01/2019 - 02/2021)

Ukraine, Donetsk

- Participated in the creation of 15+ websites.
- · Created 6 websites from zero.
- Worked directly with clients and implemented all their wishes.
- Added over 40 features for existing services.
- Built 3 messenger bots.

Tech summary: JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, React, Redux, Express.js, MySQL, Node.js, External API, Website Parsing, Figma.

Projects:

Platform which helps people to find the most suitable startups for them and vice versa

- · Developed and implemented dashboards/admin panels/work flows.
- · Optimized for search engines and improved website performance.
- Reviewed over 100 commits/merge requests.

startupium.ru

Public Excel documents parsing / creation, CITY-TRADE LTD

- · Quickly fill documents with saved data and convenient parsers.
- The ability to create your own templates.
- Abstract data storage with MongoDB.

tdd-parser.xyz

Rocket launch game for "Hxisa" travel company, Freelance

- "Falcon Heavy" launcher to the orbit.
- Combined Three.js and Cannon-es libraries to create realistic game.
- Developed special shaders and corresponding sound design.

falcon-launcher.live

Personal website of a nutritionist selling programs, Freelance

- · Business card website.
- · Data and orders management.
- The ability to design the perfect program for your needs with constructor.

ekaterina-dietolog.life

Battle City remake with online, Freelance

- Recreated "Battle City" game from Dendy.
- · Added online mode.
- Implemented new features to the game.

battle-city-remake.online

Telegram Bot helper for Wildberries.ru, Freelance

- Developed from zero managing and automation actions in your wildberries.ru seller account.
- Connected Widlberries API and Telegram API.
- Implemented subscription payment model with multiple accounts support.

github.com/miliereya/wb-telegram-bot

Education:

Donetsk National University

(09/2019 - 02/2022)

Bachelor's degree, Software Engineering